{"classes":["PERSON","TIME","DATE","ORG","GPE","EVENT","METALS","MONEY ","DISTANCE","AGE","FAC","WORK OF ART","PRODUCTS"],"annotations":[["Indian billionaire Harpal Randhawa and his son, along with four others, have been killed after their private plane crashed in southwestern Zimbabwe, PTI reported.",{"entities":[[0,6,"DATE"],[19,34,"PERSON"],[43,46,"PERSON"],[139,147,"DATE"]]}],["The plane, carrying the six including Randhawa — the owner of RioZim, a mining company producing gold and coal as well as refining nickel and copper — and his son, developed a technical fault, possibly leading to a mid-air explosion, before plunging into Peter Farm in the Zvamahande region, a Zimbabwe media website iHarare reported.",{"entities":[[38,46,"PERSON"],[131,137,"METALS"],[142,148,"METALS"],[159,162,"PERSON"],[273,283,"GPE"],[294,302,"GPE"]]}],["All passengers and crew onboard were reported dead in the accident last week.",{"entities":[[19,23,"ORG"],[58,66,"EVENT"]]}],["The single-engined Cessna 206 aircraft, owned by RioZim, was en route from Harare to the Murowa diamond mine when the accident took place on Friday. The plane crashed near the Murowa Diamonds mine, which is also partly owned by RioZim.",{"entities":[[49,55,"ORG"],[75,81,"GPE"],[89,95,"GPE"],[141,148,"DATE"],[176,196,"GPE"],[228,234,"ORG"]]}],["According to The Herald, a state-owned daily, the police said the victims included two Zimbabweans and four foreigners. “The Zimbabwe Republic Police reports a plane crash which occurred on September 29 between 7.30 am and 8 am, where six people are confirmed dead,” police said. “The Murowa Diamond Company (RioZim)-owned white and red Zcam aircraft had left Harare for the mine at 6 am and crashed about 6 km from Mashava.” ",{"entities":[[17,23,"ORG"],[50,56,"PERSON"],[87,98,"GPE"],[120,149,"ORG"],[190,202,"DATE"],[211,218,"TIME"],[223,228,"TIME"],[280,307,"ORG"],[309,315,"ORG"],[333,341,"PERSON"],[383,387,"TIME"],[406,410,"DISTANCE"]]}],["ven as the police are yet to release the names of the deceased, journalist and filmmaker Hopewell Chinono — a friend of Randhawa — confirmed his death. “I am deeply saddened by the passing of Harpal Randhawa, the owner of RioZim who died today in a plane crash in Zvishavane. Five other people including his son, who was also a pilot but a passenger on this flight, also died in the crash,” Chinono wrote on X. “My thoughts are with his wife, family, friends and the RioZim community.” ",{"entities":[[11,17,"PERSON"],[89,105,"PERSON"],[120,128,"PERSON"],[192,207,"PERSON"],[222,228,"ORG"],[249,260,"EVENT"],[264,275,"GPE"],[308,311,"PERSON"],[391,398,"PERSON"],[467,473,"ORG"]]}],["Three of the world’s 10 slowest cities in terms of traffic speeds are in India, according to the findings by a US-based private non-profit research organisation.",{"entities":[[73,78,"GPE"]]}],["As per the report, Bhiwandi in Maharashtra, Kolkata, and Bihar’s Arrah are among the 10 slowest cities in the world on the speed index.",{"entities":[[19,27,"GPE"],[31,42,"GPE"],[44,51,"GPE"],[57,64,"GPE"],[65,70,"GPE"]]}],["The study, conducted by the National Bureau of Economic Research (NBER), covered over 1,200 cities in 152 countries.",{"entities":[[28,64,"ORG"],[66,70,"ORG"]]}],["According to the report — ‘The Fast, the Slow and the Congested: Urban Transportation in Rich And Poor Countries’ — the average travel speed of motor vehicles throughout the day is the highest in Flint (US), slowest in Bangladesh capital Dhaka, and is the most congested in Bogota (Colombia).",{"entities":[[196,201,"GPE"],[203,205,"GPE"],[219,229,"GPE"],[238,243,"GPE"],[274,280,"GPE"],[282,290,"GPE"]]}],["Volunteering has a rich history in India that dates back centuries, and its nature and purpose have evolved over time. The concepts of seva (selfless service) and dharma (duty) are central to many religious and philosophical traditions in India. Movements in pre- and post-Independence India have relied on volunteers. Volunteers have also played a role in various women’s movements in independent India. However, in recent years, volunteering came to be viewed as an activity that young people only engage in to accumulate certificates to secure admissions into prestigious institutions",{"entities":[[0,12,"EVENT"],[135,139,"EVENT"],[141,157,"EVENT"],[163,175,"EVENT"]]}],["Volunteering has a rich history in India that dates back centuries, and its nature and purpose have evolved over time. The concepts of seva (selfless service) and dharma (duty) are central to many religious and philosophical traditions in India. Movements in pre- and post-Independence India have relied on volunteers. Volunteers have also played a role in various women’s movements in independent India. However, in recent years, volunteering came to be viewed as an activity that young people only engage in to accumulate certificates to secure admissions into prestigious institutions",{"entities":[[135,139,"EVENT"],[141,157,"EVENT"],[163,169,"EVENT"],[171,176,"EVENT"]]}],["“Our first plan is to control pollution in Delhi. The second thing that is part of our winter action plan is coordinating with the states where stubble burning happens. Punjab has also prepared this time. According to reports, there will be less stubble burning in Punjab,\" Delhi Environment Minister Gopal Rai said.",{"entities":[[30,39,"EVENT"],[43,49,"GPE"],[169,175,"GPE"],[265,271,"GPE"],[274,300,"ORG"],[301,310,"PERSON"]]}],["US has clarified its stance on the India-Canada diplomatic crisis stemmed from Trudeau's allegations that India got Sikh separatist leader Hardeep Singh Nijjar killed in Canada. Before external affairs minister S Jaishankar met US Secretary of State Antony Blinken in Washington, the US said it favoured an investigation into the allegations levelled by Canada and wanted India to cooperate in that. India reiterated that the allegations are baseless and Canada did not provide any specific information in connection to this. Canada, however, said it shared information with India many weeks ago.",{"entities":[[0,2,"GPE"],[35,47,"GPE"],[79,88,"PERSON"],[139,159,"PERSON"],[170,177,"GPE"],[211,223,"PERSON"],[250,264,"PERSON"],[268,278,"GPE"],[354,360,"GPE"],[372,377,"GPE"],[455,461,"GPE"],[526,532,"GPE"]]}],["A Delhi court on Wednesday granted bail to former Bihar chief minister and Rashtriya Janata Dal chief, Lalu Yadav, former Bihar CM Rabri Devi, Bihar deputy CM Tejashwi Yadav and RJD MP Misa Bharti in the alleged land-for-jobs scam case.",{"entities":[[2,7,"GPE"],[17,26,"DATE"],[27,39,"EVENT"],[50,55,"GPE"],[75,95,"ORG"],[103,113,"PERSON"],[131,141,"PERSON"],[159,173,"PERSON"],[190,196,"PERSON"]]}],["Delhi court grants bail to Lalu Yadav, Tejashwi Yadav in alleged job scam.",{"entities":[[0,11,"ORG"],[27,37,"PERSON"],[39,53,"PERSON"]]}],["India celebrates its Teachers' Day on September 5 to mark the birth anniversary of Dr Sarvepalli Radhakrishnan. However, globally, Teachers' Day falls a month later on October 5. World Teachers' Day, or International Teachers' Day, marks the anniversary of the adoption of the 1966 ILO and UNESCO recommendation on the status of teachers. The recommendation set benchmarks around the rights and responsibilities of teachers.",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"],[21,34,"EVENT"],[38,49,"DATE"],[83,85,"PERSON"],[86,111,"PERSON"],[131,144,"EVENT"],[168,178,"DATE"],[179,198,"EVENT"],[203,230,"EVENT"],[277,281,"DATE"],[282,285,"ORG"],[290,296,"ORG"]]}],["Luis Diaz's goal for Liverpool at Tottenham was mistakenly disallowed by the officials; VAR failed to overturn an incorrect offside call after believing the on-field decision had been to award the goal; PGMOL admitted VAR officials Darren England and Dan Cook failed to act",{"entities":[[0,9,"PERSON"],[21,30,"ORG"],[34,43,"ORG"],[232,246,"PERSON"],[251,259,"PERSON"]]}],["Lionel Messi Bought a $10.8 Million Home in Fort Lauderdale—the Biggest Winners Are His Neighbors",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[22,35,"MONEY "],[44,63,"GPE"]]}],["Soccer superstar Lionel Messi is raising the sport’s profile not only in Miami but the U.S.—and his purchase of a $10.75 million estate is now drawing curious eyes from around the world to a gated community he now calls home in Fort Lauderdale.   ",{"entities":[[17,29,"PERSON"],[73,78,"GPE"],[87,95,"GPE"],[114,128,"MONEY "],[228,243,"GPE"]]}],["When the 36-year-old forward signed with Inter Miami CF earlier this summer—fresh off his victory during the World Cup in Qatar last year—Messi Mania hit Miami, with stalwart fans and the newly initiated lining up for tickets and merch. Although the real estate market may not go quite as crazy, it’s not immune to the hype, industry experts said. ",{"entities":[[9,20,"AGE"],[41,55,"ORG"],[109,118,"EVENT"],[122,127,"GPE"],[154,159,"GPE"]]}],["“A buyer with a massive international following is a magnet for attention, and ever since the news broke that Messi was house hunting in Fort Lauderdale, and then closed on a home in Bay Colony, all eyes have been on the area,” said Chad Carroll with the Carroll Group at Compass. “A new high-profile neighbor like Messi will up the ante for the neighborhood, which is already one of the most exclusive in the city.”",{"entities":[[3,8,"PERSON"],[110,115,"PERSON"],[137,152,"GPE"],[238,245,"ORG"],[255,268,"ORG"],[315,320,"PERSON"]]}],["Live Champions League 2023/24 group tables, results and fixtures; Man Utd lose 3-2 to Galatasaray, Arsenal beaten 2-1 at Lens; Newcastle, Man City, Celtic all in action on Wednesday   ",{"entities":[[5,21,"EVENT"],[22,29,"DATE"],[86,97,"ORG"],[99,106,"ORG"],[127,136,"ORG"],[138,146,"ORG"],[172,181,"DATE"]]}],["In-form Julian Alvarez netted twice and Rodri sealed the win as Manchester City came from behind against Red Star on matchday one. They travel to RB Leipzig, who held Harry Kane's Bayern Munich to a draw on Saturday.",{"entities":[[8,22,"PERSON"],[40,45,"PERSON"],[105,113,"ORG"],[146,156,"ORG"],[167,177,"PERSON"],[180,193,"ORG"],[207,215,"DATE"]]}],["Celtic, beaten by Feyenoord in their opening match, now host Lazio, managed by former Chelsea boss Maurizio Sarri. The Rome-based side visit Glasgow having won only two of their first seven Serie A games, and after a 2-0 defeat by Milan on Saturday.",{"entities":[[0,6,"ORG"],[18,27,"ORG"],[61,66,"ORG"],[99,114,"PERSON"],[240,248,"DATE"]]}],["Plus: Bayern Munich inspired by substitute Thomas Muller as they come from behind to beat Danish side Copenhagen to go top of Group A as Man Utd drop to bottom after defeat to Galatasaray; Bellingham has eight goals and three assists in nine games for Real Madrid, who top Group C",{"entities":[[6,19,"ORG"],[43,56,"PERSON"],[189,199,"PERSON"]]}],["1. Apple Inc. is a technology company headquartered in Cupertino, California. ",{"entities":[[3,13,"ORG"],[55,64,"DATE"],[66,76,"DATE"]]}],["  It was founded by Steve Jobs, Steve Wozniak, and Ronald Wayne in 1976.",{"entities":[[20,30,"PERSON"],[32,45,"PERSON"],[51,63,"PERSON"],[67,71,"DATE"]]}],["2. The Great Wall of China is one of the most famous landmarks in the world. ",{"entities":[[3,26,"FAC"]]}],["  It stretches over 13,000 miles and was built over several centuries.",{"entities":[[20,32,"DISTANCE"]]}],["3.Jane Austen was an English novelist known for her novels such as \"Pride and Prejudice\" and \"Sense and Sensibility.\" ",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"]]}],["   She lived in the early 19th century.",{"entities":[[26,38,"DATE"]]}],["4. Paris, often called the \"City of Love,\" is the capital of France. ",{"entities":[[3,8,"GPE"],[61,67,"GPE"]]}],["   It is known for its iconic Eiffel Tower and delicious cuisine.",{"entities":[[30,42,"FAC"]]}],["5. The Apollo 11 mission, led by astronauts Neil Armstrong, Buzz Aldrin, and Michael Collins, ",{"entities":[[3,16,"EVENT"],[44,58,"PERSON"],[60,71,"PERSON"],[77,92,"PERSON"]]}],["   successfully landed the first humans on the moon in 1969.",{"entities":[[55,59,"DATE"]]}],["6. Tesla, Inc. is an electric car and clean energy company founded by Elon Musk. ",{"entities":[[3,9,"ORG"],[70,79,"PERSON"]]}],["   It is based in Palo Alto, California.",{"entities":[[18,27,"PERSON"],[29,39,"GPE"]]}],["7. Albert Einstein, a renowned physicist, is best known for his theory of relativity. ",{"entities":[[3,18,"PERSON"]]}],["   He was born in Ulm, Germany, in 1879.",{"entities":[[18,21,"GPE"],[23,30,"GPE"],[35,39,"DATE"]]}],["8. The Amazon Rainforest, located in South America, is the largest tropical rainforest in the world. ",{"entities":[[3,24,"FAC"],[37,50,"GPE"]]}],["   It is home to a wide variety of plant and animal species.",{"entities":[[35,59,"EVENT"]]}],["31. The meeting is scheduled for 10:30 AM tomorrow at our office in New York City.",{"entities":[[8,15,"EVENT"],[33,41,"TIME"],[42,50,"DATE"],[68,76,"GPE"]]}],["32. On December 7, 1941, the attack on Pearl Harbor marked the United States' entry into World War II.",{"entities":[[7,23,"DATE"],[39,51,"GPE"],[63,76,"GPE"],[89,101,"EVENT"]]}],["33. The flight to Paris leaves at 3:45 PM from Heathrow Airport, Terminal 2.",{"entities":[[18,23,"GPE"],[34,41,"TIME"],[47,63,"GPE"]]}],["26. The Red Square in Moscow, Russia, is a historic and cultural center, known for landmarks like the Kremlin and Saint Basil's Cathedral. It has hosted many significant events.",{"entities":[[4,18,"GPE"],[22,28,"GPE"],[30,36,"GPE"]]}],["27. Albert Camus, a French philosopher and author, is celebrated for his existentialist works, including \"The Stranger\" and \"The Myth of Sisyphus.\"",{"entities":[[4,16,"PERSON"]]}],["28. The Panama Canal, connecting the Atlantic and Pacific Oceans, is a cru",{"entities":[[8,20,"FAC"],[37,45,"GPE"],[50,64,"GPE"]]}],["12. Google LLC is a multinational technology company that specializes in internet-related services and products. It was founded by Larry Page and Sergey Brin while they were Ph.D. students at Stanford University.",{"entities":[[4,14,"ORG"],[131,141,"PERSON"],[146,157,"PERSON"],[192,211,"FAC"]]}],["13. The Nile River is the longest river in the world, flowing through northeastern Africa. It is a vital water source for many countries in the region.",{"entities":[[4,18,"FAC"],[70,90,"GPE"]]}],["14. Frida Kahlo, a Mexican artist known for her self-portraits, is considered one of the most influential painters of the 20th century. She had a turbulent life and a unique artistic style.",{"entities":[[4,15,"PERSON"],[19,26,"PERSON"],[122,135,"DATE"]]}],["15. The Vatican City is the smallest independent state in the world, located within Rome, Italy. It serves as the spiritual and administrative center of the Roman Catholic Church.",{"entities":[[8,20,"GPE"],[84,88,"GPE"],[90,96,"GPE"],[157,178,"FAC"]]}],["16. Nelson Mandela, a prominent anti-apartheid revolutionary, became the first black president of South Africa in 1994. He was a symbol of resistance and reconciliation.",{"entities":[[4,18,"PERSON"],[98,110,"GPE"],[114,119,"DATE"]]}],["17. The Pacific Ocean is the largest and deepest ocean on Earth, covering more than 60 million square miles. It is home to diverse marine life, including whales, sharks, and coral reefs.",{"entities":[[8,21,"GPE"],[58,63,"GPE"],[84,108,"DISTANCE"]]}],["18. Charles Dickens, an English novelist, wrote many classic works of literature, such as \"A Tale of Two Cities\" and \"Oliver Twist.\" His writings often depicted the social issues of his time.",{"entities":[[4,19,"PERSON"],[93,111,"WORK OF ART"],[117,132,"WORK OF ART"]]}],["19. The Sahara Desert is the largest hot desert in the world, spanning across North Africa. Its vast sand dunes and extreme temperatures make it a challenging environment.",{"entities":[[8,21,"FAC"],[78,91,"FAC"]]}],["20. The Declaration of Independence, signed in 1776, marked the United States' formal declaration of independence from British rule. It is a foundational document in American history.",{"entities":[[4,35,"FAC"],[47,51,"DATE"],[64,77,"GPE"]]}],["21. Tokyo, the capital of Japan, is a bustling metropolis known for its modern technology, historic temples, and vibrant street life. It hosted the 2020 Summer Olympics.",{"entities":[[4,9,"GPE"],[26,31,"GPE"],[148,152,"DATE"],[153,168,"EVENT"]]}],["9. Shakespeare's plays, including \"Romeo and Juliet\" and \"Hamlet,\" are considered some of the greatest works of literature in the English language.",{"entities":[[3,14,"PERSON"],[35,51,"WORK OF ART"],[57,64,"WORK OF ART"]]}],["10. Mount Everest, the world's highest peak, is part of the Himalayan mountain range in Asia. ",{"entities":[[4,17,"FAC"],[88,92,"GPE"]]}],["    Climbers from around the world attempt to reach its summit.",{"entities":[[29,34,"GPE"]]}],["11. The Mona Lisa, painted by Leonardo da Vinci, is displayed in the Louvre Museum in Paris. ",{"entities":[[8,17,"PERSON"],[30,47,"PERSON"],[69,82,"PERSON"],[86,91,"GPE"]]}],["    It is one of the most famous paintings in history.",{"entities":[]}],["31. The meeting is scheduled for 10:30 AM tomorrow at our office in New York City.",{"entities":[[8,15,"EVENT"],[33,41,"TIME"],[42,50,"DATE"],[68,76,"GPE"]]}],["32. On December 7, 1941, the attack on Pearl Harbor marked the United States' entry into World War II.",{"entities":[[7,23,"DATE"],[39,51,"GPE"],[63,76,"GPE"],[89,101,"EVENT"]]}],["33. The flight to Paris leaves at 3:45 PM from Heathrow Airport, Terminal 2.",{"entities":[[18,23,"GPE"],[34,41,"TIME"]]}],["34. In the 1980s, the personal computer revolutionized the way people work and communicate.",{"entities":[[11,16,"DATE"]]}],["35. The train departs from Chicago Union Station at 9:15 AM every morning.",{"entities":[[27,34,"GPE"],[52,59,"TIME"]]}],["36. Shakespeare's \"Macbeth\" is set in Scotland during the 11th century.",{"entities":[[4,15,"PERSON"],[19,26,"PERSON"],[58,70,"DATE"]]}],["37. The conference call is scheduled for 2:00 PM on October 15th, 2023.",{"entities":[[8,23,"EVENT"],[41,48,"TIME"],[52,70,"DATE"]]}],["38. The Olympic Games are held every four years, with the next event scheduled for 2024 in Paris.",{"entities":[[4,21,"EVENT"],[63,78,"EVENT"],[83,87,"DATE"],[91,96,"GPE"]]}],["39. The sun sets over the horizon at 7:30 PM in the summer months.",{"entities":[[8,16,"EVENT"],[37,44,"TIME"]]}],["40. The Great Depression of the 1930s had a profound impact on the global economy.",{"entities":[[4,24,"FAC"],[32,37,"DATE"]]}],["41. Daylight Saving Time begins on the second Sunday in March and ends on the first Sunday in November.",{"entities":[[46,52,"DATE"],[56,61,"DATE"],[84,90,"DATE"],[94,102,"DATE"]]}],["42. The movie premiere is set for 8:00 PM on Friday, November 10th, at the historic theater downtown.",{"entities":[[34,41,"TIME"],[45,51,"DATE"],[53,66,"DATE"]]}],["43. The lunar eclipse will be visible at 11:45 PM tonight.",{"entities":[[41,49,"TIME"]]}],["44. The Renaissance period, characterized by artistic and cultural rebirth, occurred in Europe from the 14th to the 17th century.",{"entities":[[8,19,"EVENT"],[88,94,"GPE"],[104,108,"DATE"],[116,129,"DATE"]]}],["45. The restaurant opens for lunch at 11:00 AM and serves dinner until 10:00 PM.",{"entities":[[38,46,"TIME"],[71,80,"TIME"]]}],["46. The concert starts at 7:00 PM sharp, so please arrive on time.",{"entities":[[8,15,"EVENT"],[26,33,"TIME"]]}],["47. The Space Shuttle Challenger disaster occurred on January 28, 1986.",{"entities":[[4,41,"EVENT"],[54,70,"DATE"]]}],["48. The marathon race begins at sunrise, around 6:00 AM.",{"entities":[[4,21,"EVENT"],[48,55,"TIME"]]}],["49. The company's annual report is due by the end of the fiscal year on December 31st.",{"entities":[[72,86,"DATE"]]}],["50. The museum is open to the public from 10:00 AM to 6:00 PM every day except Mondays.",{"entities":[[42,50,"TIME"],[54,61,"TIME"],[79,86,"DATE"]]}],["With Maharashtra Deputy Chief Minister Ajit Pawar excusing himself from the cabinet meeting on Tuesday and not accompanying Chief Minister Eknath Shinde and Deputy Chief Minister Devendra Fadnavis to Delhi, the Opposition has described his absenteeism as a “political illness” that could rock the government.",{"entities":[[39,49,"PERSON"],[139,152,"PERSON"],[170,196,"PERSON"],[200,205,"GPE"]]}],["“Ajit Pawar seems to be suffering from political illness…He is apparently upset over the delay in appointment of district guardian ministers,” said Opposition leader Vijay Wadettiwar. Months after joining the Shinde-Fadnavis government, a few ministers from the Ajit Pawar-led Nationalist Congress Party (NCP) are yet to be assigned responsibilities as district guardian ministers.",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[166,183,"PERSON"],[209,224,"PERSON"],[277,303,"ORG"],[305,308,"ORG"]]}],["“It has just been three months since the triple engine government came to power…and I have heard that one faction is upset,” NCP MP Supriya Sule said. “I heard that the faction which is upset met Fadnavis and conveyed their resentment to him. In three months, the honeymoon is not yet over, and already problems have started cropping up. In just three months, such news is surfacing…Who is running the government?” she asked.",{"entities":[[125,128,"ORG"],[132,144,"PERSON"]]}],["NCP minister Chhagan Bhujbal, who belongs to the Ajit Pawar faction, said, “Ajit dada had a throat infection and therefore could not go to Delhi. Today (Tuesday), the cabinet meeting was held and we received a message that he was not well. If Ajit dada could not make it to the cabinet meeting from his residence, how will he go to Delhi?”",{"entities":[[0,3,"ORG"],[13,28,"PERSON"],[49,59,"PERSON"],[139,145,"GPE"],[153,160,"DATE"],[167,182,"EVENT"],[243,252,"PERSON"],[332,337,"GPE"]]}],["NCP spokesperson Sanjay Tatkare also told The Indian Express that Ajit Pawar has a throat infection. “He is not in a position to speak and has a little fever as well. He is taking rest at home,” he said.",{"entities":[[0,3,"ORG"],[17,31,"PERSON"],[66,76,"PERSON"]]}],["In Pune, BJP leader Chandrakant Patil is the district guardian minister, a post that Ajit Pawar wants for himself. The BJP, however, is reluctant to give it up.",{"entities":[[3,7,"GPE"],[9,12,"ORG"],[20,37,"PERSON"],[85,95,"PERSON"],[119,122,"ORG"]]}],["Flipkart was founded in October 2007 in Mumbai by Sachin Bansal and Binny Bansal, alumni of the IIT, Delhi and former Amazon employees.[9][10][11] The company initially focused on online book sales with country-wide shipping. Flipkart slowly grew in prominence and was receiving 100 orders per day by 2008.[12]",{"entities":[[0,8,"ORG"],[24,36,"DATE"],[40,46,"GPE"],[50,63,"PERSON"],[68,80,"PERSON"],[96,99,"ORG"],[101,106,"GPE"],[118,124,"ORG"],[226,234,"ORG"]]}],["Big Billion Days Sale 2023 is here. Grab your favorite products from your wishlist at discounted prices with exciting offers. Check out the top brands with new and trending products. Explore electronic devices, fashion apparel, accessories, home decor, furniture, and more at amazing discounted rates. The Big Billion Day 2023 brings a festive mood to fill your shopping cart with essentials and more without spending much. It is also the right time to buy gadgets like laptops, mobile phones, televisions, speakers, and other electronic accessories.",{"entities":[[0,21,"EVENT"],[22,26,"DATE"],[211,218,"PRODUCTS"],[228,239,"PRODUCTS"],[241,251,"PRODUCTS"],[253,262,"PRODUCTS"],[322,326,"DATE"],[381,391,"PRODUCTS"],[457,464,"PRODUCTS"],[470,477,"PRODUCTS"],[479,492,"PRODUCTS"],[494,505,"PRODUCTS"],[507,516,"PRODUCTS"]]}],["",{"entities":[]}],["Stay tuned for the Big Billion Day Sale to amp up your wardrobe with clothes, footwear, jewelry, beauty, sports products, and more. In addition, elevate your room decor with top-brand mattresses, sofas, chairs, and other furniture available at discounted prices during the Big Billion Days Sale 2023. Also, enjoy the sales and offers on flight and hotel deals from the latest holiday packages. Big Billion leading categories like Electronics, TVs and appliances, Fashion, Beauty, and Home and furniture. You can also get amazing sales discounts and bank discounts of up to 10 percent.",{"entities":[[19,34,"EVENT"],[78,86,"PRODUCTS"],[88,95,"PRODUCTS"],[97,103,"PRODUCTS"],[105,120,"PRODUCTS"],[174,183,"PRODUCTS"],[184,194,"PRODUCTS"],[196,201,"PRODUCTS"],[203,209,"PRODUCTS"],[221,230,"PRODUCTS"],[273,289,"EVENT"],[295,300,"DATE"],[430,441,"PRODUCTS"],[443,446,"PRODUCTS"],[451,461,"PRODUCTS"],[463,470,"PRODUCTS"],[472,478,"PRODUCTS"],[484,488,"PRODUCTS"],[493,503,"PRODUCTS"]]}],["realme C53Apple iPhone 11realme 11 ProSamsung Galaxy S23 Ultra 5Gvivo V27",{"entities":[[0,6,"PRODUCTS"],[7,15,"PRODUCTS"],[16,22,"PRODUCTS"],[35,45,"PRODUCTS"],[46,56,"PRODUCTS"],[63,73,"PRODUCTS"]]}],["OnePlus 11RApple 1Phone 13 iQOO Z7 Pro",{"entities":[[0,7,"PRODUCTS"],[8,16,"PRODUCTS"],[17,23,"PRODUCTS"],[27,38,"PRODUCTS"]]}],["realme C55Apple iPhone 14 Pro MaxSamsung Galaxy A14 5GXiaomi Redmi Note 12 Pro 5G Oppo A78 5GInfinix GT 10 ProApple iPhone 12 Apple iPhone 15 Pro vivo T2x OnePlus Nord CE 3 Lite 5G Samsung Galaxy A54 5G Moto G84",{"entities":[[0,15,"PRODUCTS"],[16,25,"PRODUCTS"],[30,40,"PRODUCTS"],[126,145,"PRODUCTS"],[181,202,"PRODUCTS"]]}],["Ranveer Singh is a fourth or fifth take actor; Sonakshi Sinha nails it on second one: Vikramaditya Motwane reveals who the real one-take star is",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[47,61,"PERSON"],[86,98,"PERSON"],[99,106,"PERSON"]]}],["Shah Rukh Khan apologises to fans for being late to Jawan success event: ‘Maaf toh kar denge na?’",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[52,57,"EVENT"]]}],["1. France – 82.6 million visitors The United States – 75.6 million visitors  Spain – 75.6 million visitors China – 59.3 million visitors Italy – 52.4 million visit United Kingdom – 35.8 million visitors Germany – 35.6 million visitors Mexico – 35.0 million visitors Thailand – 32.6 million visitors Turkey – 30 million visitors Austria – 28.1 million visitors Malaysia – 26.8 million visitors Hong Kong – 26.6 million visitors Greece – 24.8 million visitors Russia – 24.6 million visitors Japan – 24.0 million visitors Canada – 20.0 million visitors Saudi Arabia – 18.0 million visitors Poland – 17.5 million visitors South Korea – 17.2 million visitors Netherlands – 15.8 million visitors Macao – 15.7 million visitors Hungary – 15.3 million visitors United Arab Emirates – 14.9 million visitors India – 14.6 million visitors Croatia – 13.8 million visitors Ukraine – 13.3 million visitors Singapore – 12.9 million visitors Indonesia – 12.0 million visitors Czech Republic – 11.9 million visitors",{"entities":[[3,9,"GPE"],[12,24,"MONEY "],[34,51,"GPE"],[54,66,"MONEY "],[77,82,"GPE"],[107,112,"GPE"],[115,127,"MONEY "],[137,142,"GPE"],[164,178,"GPE"],[203,210,"GPE"],[235,241,"GPE"],[266,274,"GPE"],[277,281,"MONEY "],[299,305,"GPE"],[328,335,"GPE"],[360,368,"GPE"],[371,383,"MONEY "],[393,402,"GPE"],[427,433,"GPE"],[458,464,"GPE"],[467,479,"MONEY "],[489,494,"GPE"],[519,525,"GPE"],[550,562,"GPE"],[565,577,"MONEY "],[587,593,"GPE"],[618,629,"GPE"],[632,644,"MONEY "],[654,665,"GPE"],[690,695,"GPE"],[720,727,"GPE"],[752,772,"GPE"],[797,802,"GPE"],[827,834,"GPE"],[859,868,"GPE"],[891,900,"GPE"],[925,934,"GPE"],[959,973,"GPE"]]}],["New York",{"entities":[[0,8,"GPE"]]}],["London",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Paris",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Tokyo",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Los Angeles",{"entities":[[0,11,"GPE"]]}],["Chicago",{"entities":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}],["Beijing",{"entities":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}],["Mumbai",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Shanghai",{"entities":[[0,8,"GPE"]]}],["Istanbul",{"entities":[[0,8,"GPE"]]}],["Cairo",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Moscow",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Sydney",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Toronto",{"entities":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}],["Rio de Janeiro",{"entities":[[0,14,"GPE"]]}],["Buenos Aires",{"entities":[[0,12,"GPE"]]}],["Dubai",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Bangkok",{"entities":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}],["Hong Kong",{"entities":[[0,9,"GPE"]]}],["Singapore",{"entities":[[0,9,"GPE"]]}],["Rome",{"entities":[[0,4,"GPE"]]}],["Madrid",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Berlin",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Amsterdam",{"entities":[[0,9,"GPE"]]}],["Athens",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Vienna",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Prague",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Budapest",{"entities":[[0,8,"GPE"]]}],["Warsaw",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Stockholm",{"entities":[[0,9,"GPE"]]}],["Helsinki",{"entities":[[0,8,"GPE"]]}],["Oslo",{"entities":[[0,4,"GPE"]]}],["Copenhagen",{"entities":[[0,10,"GPE"]]}],["Brussels",{"entities":[[0,8,"GPE"]]}],["Zurich",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Geneva",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Nairobi",{"entities":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}],["Johannesburg",{"entities":[[0,12,"GPE"]]}],["Seoul",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Jakarta",{"entities":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}],["Delhi",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Karachi",{"entities":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}],["Dhaka",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Manila",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Kuala Lumpur",{"entities":[[0,12,"GPE"]]}],["Hanoi",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Ho Chi Minh City",{"entities":[[0,16,"GPE"]]}],["Taipei",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Tel Aviv",{"entities":[[0,8,"GPE"]]}],["Santiago",{"entities":[[0,8,"GPE"]]}],["Lima",{"entities":[[0,4,"GPE"]]}],["Bogota",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["San Francisco",{"entities":[[0,13,"GPE"]]}],["San Diego",{"entities":[[0,9,"GPE"]]}],["Miami",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Dallas",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Houston",{"entities":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}],["Atlanta",{"entities":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}],["Boston",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Philadelphia",{"entities":[[0,12,"GPE"]]}],["Washington, D.C.",{"entities":[[0,16,"GPE"]]}],["Toronto",{"entities":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}],["Vancouver",{"entities":[[0,9,"GPE"]]}],["Montreal",{"entities":[[0,8,"GPE"]]}],["Calgary",{"entities":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}],["Edmonton",{"entities":[[0,8,"GPE"]]}],["Sydney",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Melbourne",{"entities":[[0,9,"GPE"]]}],["Brisbane",{"entities":[[0,8,"GPE"]]}],["Auckland",{"entities":[[0,8,"GPE"]]}],["Wellington",{"entities":[[0,10,"GPE"]]}],["Christchurch",{"entities":[[0,12,"GPE"]]}],["Perth",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Adelaide",{"entities":[[0,8,"GPE"]]}],["Johannesburg",{"entities":[[0,12,"GPE"]]}],["Cape Town",{"entities":[[0,9,"GPE"]]}],["Durban",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Pretoria",{"entities":[[0,8,"GPE"]]}],["Nairobi",{"entities":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}],["Cairo",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Alexandria",{"entities":[[0,10,"GPE"]]}],["Casablanca",{"entities":[[0,10,"GPE"]]}],["Tunis",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Algiers",{"entities":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}],["Istanbul",{"entities":[[0,8,"GPE"]]}],["Ankara",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Izmir",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Antalya",{"entities":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}],["Bursa",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Gaziantep",{"entities":[[0,9,"GPE"]]}],["Adana",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Beirut",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Amman",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Riyadh",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Jeddah",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Mecca",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"]]}],["Medina",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["Doha",{"entities":[[0,4,"GPE"]]}],["Abu Dhabi",{"entities":[[0,9,"GPE"]]}],["Riyadh",{"entities":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}],["First Female Train Driver in India: Surekha Yadav Surekha Yadav has made an indelible mark in a historically male-dominated field as she achieved the distinction of becoming India’s first female train driver in India. Basohli Pashmina, an age-old traditional craft originating from the picturesque district of Kathua in Jammu and Kashmir, has recently earned the prestigious Geographical Indication (GI) tag. This recognition not only celebrates the exceptional craftsmanship of the artisans but also protects the authenticity and uniqueness of this artisanal heritage. A Legacy of Softness and Finesse …",{"entities":[[34,49,"PERSON"],[50,63,"PERSON"],[174,181,"GPE"],[211,217,"GPE"],[218,234,"PERSON"],[310,316,"GPE"],[320,325,"GPE"],[330,337,"GPE"]]}],["Chairman of DRDO August 26, 2022, witnessed a pivotal moment in the realm of Indian defence research as Dr. Samir V Kamat took on the role of Chairman at the Defence Research and Development Organization (DRDO).",{"entities":[[12,16,"ORG"],[17,32,"DATE"],[77,83,"PERSON"],[104,121,"PERSON"],[158,209,"ORG"]]}],["India clinched gold in the compound archery mixed team final, on Day 11 of the ongoing Asian Games 2023 in Hangzhou, on Wednesday. Jyothi Surekha Vennam and Pravis Ojas Deotale were in hot form as they took India past their best Asiad medal tally. Their current tally is 71, better than their previous best in Jakarta 2018 (70). Meanwhile, India also bagged bronze in the 35km race walk mixed team final. In action, we will also have India's golden boy Neeraj Chopra, who will aim for a",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"],[65,71,"DATE"],[87,98,"EVENT"],[99,103,"DATE"],[107,115,"GPE"],[120,130,"DATE"],[131,152,"PERSON"],[157,176,"PERSON"],[310,322,"DATE"],[340,345,"GPE"],[372,376,"DISTANCE"],[434,439,"GPE"],[453,466,"PERSON"]]}],["Kishore Kumar Jena is another Indian, who'll be competing in the same event and he too would aim for a podium finish. Meawhile, Dipika Pallikal, Harinder Pal Singh Sandhu defeated Hong Kong's Ka Yi Lee, Chi Him Wong in mixed doubles semifinal, enter final. An all-Indian squash mixed doubles final was prevented as Anahat Singh, Abhay Singh lost to Malaysia's Aifa Binti and Mohammad Syafiq in the other semifinal. The pair had to settle for bronze. Parveen also lost in her 57kg women's boxing semifinal and claimed bronze.",{"entities":[[0,18,"PERSON"],[30,36,"GPE"],[128,143,"PERSON"],[145,170,"PERSON"],[180,189,"GPE"],[192,201,"PERSON"],[203,215,"PERSON"],[315,327,"PERSON"],[329,340,"PERSON"],[349,370,"PERSON"],[375,390,"PERSON"],[450,457,"PERSON"]]}],["In other track and field events we have Harmilan Bains and Chanda, who'll take part in the women's 800m finals. Harmilan will hope for a second medal at the continental event, having already won a silver medal in women's 1500m earlier in the competition. Avinash Sable, who won gold in men's 3000m steeplechase, will look to repeat his feat but in a different discipline. The long-distance runner will be in action in men's 5000m with Gulveer Singh being the other Indian also participating in the event. Gulveer too has already won a medal in the Asian Games, when he finished third in the men's 10,000m final. Apart from track and field, the Indian men's hockey team will be in action in the semifinal encounter against Korea. India have so far hammered almost every opponent and topped Pool A to qualify for the semis.",{"entities":[[40,54,"PERSON"],[59,65,"PERSON"],[157,174,"EVENT"],[221,226,"DISTANCE"],[255,268,"PERSON"],[292,297,"DISTANCE"],[424,429,"DISTANCE"],[435,448,"PERSON"],[505,512,"PERSON"],[597,604,"DISTANCE"],[722,728,"GPE"],[729,734,"GPE"]]}],["arveen loses in women's 57kg semifinal, gets BRONZE",{"entities":[]}],["Kabaddi: India men defeat Thailand 63-26 in Group A",{"entities":[[9,14,"GPE"],[26,34,"GPE"]]}],["Wrestling: Neeraj loses to Uzbekistan's Makhmud Bakhshilloev in the men's greco-roman 67kg 1/8 final",{"entities":[[11,17,"PERSON"],[27,37,"GPE"],[40,60,"PERSON"]]}],["Sunil Kumar loses to a Iran's Naser Alizadeh in the men's greco-roman 87kg semifinal",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[23,27,"GPE"],[30,44,"PERSON"]]}],["Athletics: India win BRONZE in 35km race mixed team final",{"entities":[[11,16,"GPE"],[31,35,"DISTANCE"]]}],["Badminton: PV Sindhu defeats Indonesia's Putri Kusuma Wardani to advance to women's singles quarterfinals",{"entities":[[11,20,"PERSON"],[29,38,"GPE"],[41,61,"PERSON"]]}],["HS Prannoy defeats Kazakhstan's Dmitriy Panarin to enter men's singles quarterfinal",{"entities":[[0,10,"PERSON"],[19,29,"GPE"],[32,47,"PERSON"]]}],["India's Treesa Jolly, Gayatri Gopichand lose to South Korea's Soyeong Kim and Heeyong Kong in women's doubles pre-quarterfinals",{"entities":[[0,5,"GPE"],[8,20,"PERSON"],[22,39,"PERSON"],[48,61,"GPE"],[62,73,"PERSON"],[78,90,"PERSON"]]}],["Volleyball: India women defeated Nepal, 3-1 in Pool G",{"entities":[[12,17,"GPE"],[33,38,"GPE"]]}],["Catch the LIVE updates of the Asian Games, Day 11:",{"entities":[]}],["",{"entities":[]}],["",{"entities":[]}],["",{"entities":[]}],["",{"entities":[]}]]}